missworld.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy - Miss World - Miss World

Privacy Policy

Miss World Limited is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to www.missworld.com. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. 

By remaining on this site you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy. 

### **1\. Information that we collect from you**

When you register or download material from this site you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, contact details and company or business identity. We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from e-mails or letters you send to us.   

### **2\. Use of your information**

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of our site and to supply services you have requested. We will also use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business and services. 

In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the site or our services. We might also use your information to let you know about other products and services which we offer which may be of interest to you including and we may contact you by post, telephone or fax, as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know. 

### **3\. Disclosure of your information**

The information you provide to us will be held on our servers in the United Kingdom and may be accessed by or given to our staff working outside the UK and third parties who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes approved by you. In addition we may for business reasons move the storage location of such data outside of the UK. Where we do we will endeavour to ensure that appropriate security measures are in place regarding such data storage.

We may also allow carefully selected third parties, including other companies in our group, to contact you occasionally about products and services which may be of interest to you. They may contact you by post, telephone or fax, as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted by these companies in the future, please let us know.

Finally, if our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners. 

Countries outside the European Economic Area do not always have strong data protection laws. However, we will always take steps to ensure that your information is used by third parties in accordance with this policy. 

Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent. 

### **4\. Cookies**

Cookies are small amounts of information which we store on your computer. Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your details to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site. 

### **5\. Security and data retention**

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

###  **6\. Accessing and updating**

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. We are entitled by law to charge a fee of �10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

### **7\. Changes to our privacy policy**

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.

###  **8\. Contact**

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to [missworld@missworld.com](mailto:missworld@missworld.com)

Thank you for reading our Privacy Policy. 

This privacy policy was prepared for us by [legalcentre.co.uk](http://www.legalcentre.co.uk/) who specialise in website documentation.
